# Felipe Dolago

Cedar Park, TX 78613 | +01 (254) 681-7065 | lagofelipe@gmail.com

# **PROFILE**

Adaptable and dedicated professional with over a decade of Account Management, Customer Interaction and Data Analysis experience leading and managing cross-functional teams and delivering customer-centric marketing strategies and solutions to increase productivity and drive business revenue. Outstanding communication, analytical, problem-solving, leadership, interpersonal and teamwork abilities. Fluent in English, Spanish and Portuguese.

### **SKILLS**

Business Analyst | Project Management | Business Development | Customer Success | Client Relations | Strategic Account Management | Customer Retention | B2B | Leadership | CRM | Consulting | MS Office | Analytics | SQL | RAILS | Data | SalesForce | SAP | GSA Ready | Top Secret Clearance

# **EXPERIENCE**

Hays City Corp. Austin, TX, USA

Tex-con Oil & Motiva Enterprises Partnership - Strategic Account Manager November 2014 – July 2020

- Consistently meet or exceed all production goals and Delivery targets (2020 Motiva Marketer of the year)
- Boosted baseline workload and efficiency by moving all planning and ordering into SmartLogix. Lead time changed from 24 to 48 hrs, a 100% improvement in transit and delivery times.
- Helped to achieve team member retention in a very competitive tech and sales market, introducing cross-training to increase team redundancy to eliminate the risk of single experts, reversed a previously high turnover department
- Managed a high profile Fortune 500 partner, Total > 100M in Yearly Sales (FY2019)

Suncoast Resources Inc.

Houston, TX, USA

Suncoast Resources Austin, Operations – Warehouse Manager

July 2012-November 2014

- Lead a team in verifying and inspecting shipments in order to ensure delivery of optimal quality merchandise while improving safety scores and lead times.
- Managed location inventory, prepared and completed monthly inventory reporting.

U.S. Army Gunsan, South Korea

AMEED MEDPROS certified Trainer

- March 2010 -July 2012
- Healthcare Specialist(68W) with Top Secret Clearance assigned to USAF 8th Wing. (Kunsan AFB, South Korea)
- Primarily oversaw and trained officer personnel on MEDPROS (USMEDACC) software and its initial implementation in the Asian theater.

#### **HEI Hotels and Resorts INC.**

Orlando, FL. USA

Embassy Suites Downtown Orlando Operations- Assistant Controller

- December 2008- February 2010
- Worked directly with Controller and General Manager to ensure accuracy and auditing of all house, payables and receivable accounts.
- Assisted in the preparation of financial statements in compliance with government and Hilton guidelines and requirements

# **EDUCATION**

Flatiron School

Austin, TX, USA

August 2020

Software Engineering immersive Bootcamp

United States Army Medical Center and School AMEED Health Care Specialist / MEDPROS

San Antonio, TX, USA November 2010

Universidade Gama Filho

Bachelor of Business Administration (BBA)

Rio De Janeiro, Brazil

July 2008